<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CATcha</string>
    <string name="kitchen">kitchen</string>
    <string name="play">game</string>
    <string name="bath">bathroom</string>
    <string name="sleep">bedroom</string>
    <string name="info">info</string>
    <string name="breed_info_message">инфа о породе</string>
    <string name="breed_info_title">Breed</string>
    <string name="breed1">street</string>
    <string name="breed2">russian blue</string>
    <string name="breed3">scottish fold</string>
    <string name="breed1_info">Mongrel cats come in a variety of colors, sizes and shapes.
        Most often, striped individuals are found among mongrel cats. Usually this color is called "rustic".
        Most often they are calm, grateful, and respond vividly to the caresses of the owner.
        Many infections that cats encountered during their wandering life and somehow miraculously survived them are no longer terrible to them;
        their health is somewhat stronger than their purebred counterparts, therefore, their life expectancy is longer.
    </string>
    <string name="breed2_info">Representatives of this breed have an average size and a fairly muscular elongated body.
        At the same time, their paws are straight and long, with pink-purple pads, and the tail is thin and elongated.
        The skull of the Russian blue cat is elongated, the muzzle is flat with a straight nose.
        Her ears are large, pointed and tilted slightly forward. They
are distinguished by "aristocratic" manners and tact, have a calm disposition and intelligence.
        Animals are moderately affectionate and accommodating, but at the same time they can be independent, and they will not do something under duress.
        They are not vindictive, nor are they prone to deliberate sabotage.
        Russian blue calm tolerates loneliness and gets along well with children — tolerates pranks,
        without losing his composure and without releasing his claws. Despite this, it is better not to leave her and a small child unattended.
    </string>
    <string name="breed3_info">Softness and roundness of forms are the main general characteristics of the appearance of the Scottish fold cat.
        All body lines must be smooth – no sharp corners.
        Even the tips of the paws of these cats are small, round and neat.
        The head of the Scottish fold is often compared to an owl: it should also be of a regular round shape.
        The cheeks of the Scots are plump and very noticeable, the nose is small, the eyes are large and round.
        Because of this, cats always look as if slightly surprised.
        And the color of the pets eyes should match the color of its fur. In
        addition to the touching appearance, the Scottish fold cat also has a wonderful character.
        Initially, they were bred exclusively as domestic cats, so they turned out to be calm and affectionate pets,
        who really appreciate the comfort and convenience. They will be quite comfortable in a city apartment.
        And the owners will not get tired of an overly energetic cat. The Scottish fold will not suit
        mad jumps through the rooms, running on tables, cabinets and walls, but from time to time he will not refuse to run for a bow.
    </string>
    <string name="advice">advice</string>
    <string name="red">red</string>
    <string name="green">green</string>
    <string name="blue">blue</string>
    <string name="choose_color">Choose a background color</string>
    <string name="bath_advice">By nature, cats are very clean.
        But, one way or another, periodically the owner should wash his pet, especially if he happens to be outside.
        Frequent washing washes away the protective barrier, and the animals skin may become more sensitive.
        It is recommended to wash a domestic cat on average once every three months, a street cat - once every 4-6 weeks.
        The exception is those cases when the animals coat is heavily contaminated or it has parasites.
        You should plan bathing for a time when the cat is tired and relaxed.
        For example, after a long game – so she will have less strength to resist.
        Prepare everything you need for washing in advance – shampoo (special for cats), towel, comb, containers.
        The bathroom should be warm, about 22-24 degrees.
        Also prepare a warm place where you can dry the cat
        (to do this, first wrap the pet in a dry towel, and then you can use a hair dryer at the lowest rpm)
        If the animal is afraid of the sight of pouring water, fill it in a large basin in advance,
        gently water the animal, gradually washing off the foam.
        It is recommended to stroke the cat during the pouring process, evenly distributing water over the coat.
        The water should be a little warm, but not hot.
        You can talk to the animal in the process in a calm, friendly voice.
        This will help him relax a little.
    </string>
    <string name="kitchen_advice"> What to consider when choosing a feed: \n
        - age of the animal — kittens need more high-calorie food, and aging cats need more fiber; \n
        - individual needs — free range of the animal, overweight, pregnancy; \n
        - pathologies — for example, with urolithiasis and kidney failure, dietary food is needed. \n
        Dry and semi-dry food: \n
        It is most convenient for owners who feed pets on a free schedule:
        if you pour dry food into a bowl in the morning, it will remain fresh and tasty until the evening.
        This is also a suitable option for cases when you need to leave for 1-2 days and leave the cat alone.
        Its main drawback is that there is practically no moisture in it, so the animal should always have
        fresh water in a bowl, a water dispenser or a drinking fountain. \n
        Wet food: \n
        Suitable for sick and recovering cats, as well as old animals who find it difficult to chew pellets-crackers.
        There is enough liquid in this feed, so cats drink very little.
        The main disadvantage is that it deteriorates quickly. If the cat did not eat the portion immediately, after half an hour the product is frozen,
        and by the evening it dries up. \n
        Experts believe that it is permissible to give a cat both "drying" and canned food at once. But it is important not to mix
        different types of feed in one bowl and choose the feed from the same manufacturer.
        Products of different companies are mixed, just to transfer the cat from one species to another.

    </string>
    <string name="sleep_advice">Healthy sleep of an adult cat should be long, at least 14-16 hours a day.
        Kittens sleep more than adult pets. The
pet will sleep well if its other needs are covered.
        To sleep well, a pet needs a suitable permanent place where he will feel safe.
        Also, the cat should be well fed and healthy. \n
For a nocturnal predator, activity in the dark is the norm.
        But if the cat does not let you sleep at night, you need to think about what to do about it.
        To rebuild the cats daily routine is real, you need to gradually increase the level of activity in the daytime.
        If the animal spends a lot of energy during the day, then at night it is guaranteed to be able to sleep soundly.
Alarm signal – the cat hides under the sofa, in the closet or somewhere else in a place inaccessible to people, and sleeps for a long time.
        This is a sign of severe stress or illness.</string>
    <string name="mouse">Mouse cought:</string>
    <string name="learning">Learning</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="catalog">Catalog</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="care_points">Care points:</string>
    <string name="number_of_cats">Number of available cats:</string>
    <string name="title1">Do you want to take the cat to yourself?</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="title2">You don\'t have enough care points</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="on">Turn on the sound</string>
    <string name="off">Turn off the sound</string>
    <string name="change_language">Русский</string>
    <string name="buy">Do you want to buy a product?</string>
    <string name="cp">CP:</string>
    <string name="age">Age:</string>
    <string name="breed">Breed:</string>
    <string name="fish">fish</string>
    <string name="sausage">sausage</string>
    <string name="milk">milk</string>
    <string name="catjelly">catjelly</string>
    <string name="surprise">surprise</string>
    <string name="busy">your cat is already busy right now</string>
</resources>
